through June 30th of 2022, which did encompass several of the phase one technical conferences.
And so this will be applied to their previous year's contract.
Is this why we're just increased to budget?
No.
Okay.
And the benefit we get from this is what?
From the work that they're doing.
From that just a little bit.
So you talk in your, in your, in your, in your BA, you talk about, um, for the 2D modeling.
What is that before us?
So specifically this allows us to be able to evaluate some of the technical work that's being done.
And make sure that we're, the right tools are being used, the right data's being used because.
Right now a lot of the modeling and everything that's being done is being done by GRDA.
Right.
And we found some issues with some of the things that they were doing.
They also ran into some issues where they were not going to do some specific data modeling.
Because they said the software tool that they were being required to use by FERC would not accomplish that particular task.
Turns out that tetrachec was involved in the development of that software and was able to step up and say, yes, it can do that.
And here's how and why.
So that was one great example of how they were able to to step in and add significant value to the entire relationship process.
But also been able to take the data that that they can get access to and then be able to run the modeling to look at the effect that the sedimentation has on the flow of water through or the lack of flow of water.
And as it goes down the neosho river or hits twin bridges where there's another significant sedimentation hump that restricts water flow.
So are we seeing any significant differences in what these this group tetrachecs finding versus what GRDA is saying.
Yes.
And is that in our favor or against our favor.
That a fair question.
Yes.
Let's say most slide.
Somewhat subjective but for the most part in our favor.
There's been some that we point it out just to be helpful to make sure that FERC is getting all the right data.
But for the most part, yeah.
I would say very helpful.
Make a motion we approve.
Second.
Are there any more parks?
Hi.
11, good old stratton, Edmunds, and Palmer, LLC,
Coyenne for Penscola,romantic and rule curve,
and the amount of $576.10.
So what you have in the air pack,
it is actually two separate BAs
because we split this particular invoice across two
different fiscal years.
$30 of this invoice,
went against the fiscal year 2122,
to the remaining $546 in 10 cents when it gets $22.23 fiscal year.
This particular invoice, primarily, was focused on the legal process, including review
of recent GERDA, inferred filings, and the proper response to those filings.
It's kind of cool to see why I'm at this level.
No, right?
Motion to approve.
Is that a double per cent per cent per per cent per per cent?
12 other new business, if any, that is the reasons of supposing of this agenda.
13 staff reports, 14 trustee community announcements.
Let me just stop there.
Well, if we can go ahead and reconvene, do number 15, reconvene, reconvene.
This meeting will be continued from the council chambers, reconvene, and the staff rooms
for the purpose of the...